sprint.ly 2019-04-20

# Privacy Policy - sprint.ly

## INTRODUCTION

In this Privacy Policy references to we, us or our means Flow Canon LLC (doing business as Sprintly) a limited liability company based in the United States, with our mailing address located at 970 W Broadway Ste E-152, Jackson, Wyoming, 83001, United States; and

References to you or your means the person accessing and using the sprint.ly website, including our blogs (collectively, the “Website”) and/or ordering products or services that we make available to you via the Website (collectively, the “Services”).

This Privacy Policy sets out the basis on which we collect and use personal information about you through your use of the Website and the Services.

This Privacy Policy describes in detail who is responsible for the personal information that we collect about you, what personal information we collect, how we will use such personal information, who we may disclose it to and your rights and choices in relation to your personal information.

In this Privacy Policy where we use the words personal information we use these words to describe information that is about you and which identifies you.

#### WHO IS RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT?

We are the data controller for the purpose of data protection law, in respect of your personal information collected and used through your use of the Website and the Services. This is because we dictate the purpose for which your personal information is used and how we use your personal information.

#### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE HOLD ABOUT YOU?

_Information You Provide to Us_

We collect and use personal information about you in the course of providing the Website and the Services. The information that you provide to us may include the following:

|   
---|---  
Contact information | Name, shipping address, billing address, email address and telephone number  
Account information | Username, order history  
Marketing preferences, marketing activities and customer feedback | Marketing preferences

To improve our marketing communications, we may collect information about interaction with, and responses to, our marketing communications  
  
Other information you provide to us | For example, if you write a review of our Services or provide other information to us in the course of your use of our Website or Services  
  
##### This information may be provided:

  * in the course of communications between you and us (including by phone, email, chat, Website or otherwise);
  * when you register for an account;
  * when you order or inquire about Services;
  * when you sign up for our newsletter or other materials; and
  * when you report a problem with our Website or Services.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

We may also collect personal information about you through your use of the Website and the Services. This information includes online activity information and technical information about your usage activities, to the extent that such information constitutes personal information.

We collect technical information automatically through your electronic device, such as your IP address (i.e. your computer’s address on the internet), operating system type (Windows or Mac) and version, internet browser type and version, and language. We also collect information about your use of our Website, for example dates and times of log-in and out to your account, time spent on pages and the pages visited. We use this information to ensure that the Website and the Services function properly. Please also see additional information on our cookie usage in Section 5 below.

### COOKIES

The Website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of the Website. Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the device you are using. Cookies allow us to recognize your device and to collect information such as internet browser type, time spent using Services, and pages visited. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse the Website and also allows us to improve the Website.  
We may use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively, and to personalize your experience while using the Services. In addition, we may use the information to gather statistical information about the usage of the Services in order to understand how they are used, continually improve their design and functionality, and assist us with resolving questions about them. Cookies further allow us to present to you the advertisements or offers that are most likely to appeal to you. We may also use cookies to track your responses to our advertisements and we may use cookies or other files to track your use of other websites.  
You can refuse to accept the cookies we use by adjusting your browser settings. However, if you do not accept these cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Website and some online Services.

### HOW DO WE USE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU?

We use your personal information in connection with the provision of the Website and the Services to you. In particular, your personal information may be used by us, our employees, service providers, and disclosed to third parties for the following purposes. For each of these purposes, we have set out the legal basis on which we use your personal information.

Purpose | Legal Basis  
---|---  
To communicate with you and other individuals | For our legitimate business purposes (i.e., the provision of the Website and our Services)  
To provide you with the Website and the Services | For our legitimate business purposes (i.e., the provision of the Website and our Services), and depending on the circumstances, to perform a contract between you and us  
To notify you about changes to the Website or the Services | For our legitimate business purposes (i.e., the provision of the Website and our Services)  
To audit and monitor the use of the Website | For our legitimate business purposes (i.e., the provision of the Website and our Services, as well as to improve and monitor the security of the Website)

We may request your consent in circumstances where a legal justification over and above legitimate interests is required by applicable law (e.g., in relation to our use of certain cookies)  
  
To improve the quality of the Website and the Services | For our legitimate business purposes (i.e., the provision and improvement of the Website and our Services)  
To manage complaints, feedback and queries | For our legitimate business purposes (i.e., the provision and improvement of the Website and our Services)  
To carry out market research and analysis | For our legitimate business purposes (i.e., the provision, improvement and promotion of the Website and our Services)

We may request your consent in circumstances where a legal justification over and above legitimate interests is required by applicable law  
  
To carry out satisfaction surveys and analysis | For our legitimate business purposes (i.e., the provision, improvement and promotion of the Website and our Services)

We may request your consent in circumstances where a legal justification over and above legitimate interests is required by applicable law  
  
To provide you with information about the Services we offer (including details of any products which we believe may be of interest to you) in accordance with your preferences as indicated when you entered into any agreement with us, including any marketing consent preferences | For our legitimate business purposes (i.e., the provision and promotion of the Website and our Services)

We may request your consent in circumstances where a legal justification over and above legitimate interests is required by applicable law  
  
To comply with any legal or regulatory obligations (including in connection with a court order) | For our legitimate business purposes and for compliance with legal obligations to which we are subject  
To enforce or apply the agreements concerning you (including agreements between you and us) | For our legitimate business purposes and for compliance with legal obligations to which we are subject  
  
We may be required to obtain your personal information to comply with our legal requirements, to enable us to fulfil the terms of our contract with you or in preparation of us entering into a contract with you. If you do not provide the relevant personal information to us, we may not be able to provide the Website and the Services to you.

Where we rely on our legitimate business interests or those legitimate interests of a third party to justify the purposes for using your personal information, this will include:

pursuit of our commercial activities and objectives, or those of a third party;  
compliance with applicable legal and regulatory obligations and any codes of conduct;  
improvement and development of our business operations and service offering, or those of a third party; or  
protection of our business, owners, managers, employees and customers, or those of a third party.

### WHO MAY WE DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO?

You agree that we may share your personal information with:

|   
---|---  
Our service providers | Our business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors who help us provide the Website and the Services (for example, our payment services provider, marketing and advertising service providers and our shipping and other distributors )  
Our professional advisers | Including accountants, lawyers and other professional advisers that assist us in carrying out our business activities  
Government authorities and third parties involved in court action | External agencies and organisations (including the police and the relevant local authority) for the purpose of complying with applicable legal and regulatory obligations  
  
##### We may also disclose your personal information to other third parties, for example:

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets we will disclose your personal information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;
  * if we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party (or are subject to a reorganisation within our corporate group), personal information held by us will be one of the transferred assets; and
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation.

### WHERE WILL WE TRANSFER YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We are headquartered in the United States and we will process your personal information in the United States. Your personal information will be transferred and stored in the United States.

## HOW WE PROTECTION YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We implement a variety of technical and organizational measures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, disclosure and transfer.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to the Website and any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your personal information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

### HOW LONG WILL WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will retain your personal information for as long as is necessary for purposes for which it was collected. The precise period will depend on the reason why it was collected. Those periods are also based on the requirements of applicable data protection laws, applicable legal and regulatory requirements and periods relating to the commencement of legal actions.

### YOUR RIGHTS

The following is a summary of the data protection rights available to individuals in the European Union and the European Economic Area in connection with their personal information. The rights may only apply in certain circumstances and are subject to certain exemptions. Please see the table below for a summary of your rights. You can exercise these rights using the contact details at the end of this Privacy Policy.

#### Summary of your rights

|   
---|---  
Right of access to your personal information | You have the right to receive a copy of your personal information that we hold about you, subject to certain exemptions.  
Right to rectify your personal information | You have the right to ask us to correct your personal information that we hold where it is incorrect or incomplete.  
Right to erasure of your personal information. | You have the right to ask that your personal information be deleted in certain circumstances. For example (i) where your personal information is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise used; (ii) if you withdraw your consent and there is no other legal ground for which we rely on for the continued use of your personal information; (iii) if you object to the use of your personal information (as set out below); (iv) if we have used your personal information unlawfully; or (v) if your personal information needs to be erased to comply with a legal obligation. To have your information erased, please contact [support@sprint.ly](mailto:support@sprint.ly)  
Right to restrict the use of your personal information | You have the right to suspend our use of your personal information in certain circumstances. For example (i) where you think your personal information is inaccurate and only for such period to enable us to verify the accuracy of your personal information; (ii) the use of your personal information is unlawful and you oppose the erasure of your personal information and request that it is suspended instead; (iii) we no longer need your personal information, but your personal information is required by you for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; or (iv) you have objected to the use of your personal information and we are verifying whether our grounds for the use of your personal information override your objection.  
Right to data portability | You have the right to obtain your personal information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and for it to be transferred to another organization, where it is technically feasible. The right only applies where the use of your personal information is based on your consent or for the performance of a contract, and when the use of your personal information is carried out by automated (i.e. electronic) means.  
Right to object to the use of your personal information | You have the right to object to the use of your personal information in certain circumstances. For example (i) where you have grounds relating to your particular situation and we use your personal information for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party); and (ii) if you object to the use of your personal information for direct marketing purposes.  
Right to withdraw consent | You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where we rely on consent to use your personal information.  
Right to complain to the relevant data protection authority | You have the right to complain to the relevant data protection authority where you think we have not used your personal information in accordance with data protection law.  
  
## LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

The Website may contain links to the websites of third parties. We have no control over the content or operation of these websites, nor do we control the confidentiality or privacy practices of the website operators. Consequently, any personal information you submit through such websites is governed by the privacy policies of the websites in question. It is therefore your responsibility to find out about the third party policies in order to protect information that concerns you.

### NO SERVICES FOR MINORS

We do not knowingly collect information from minors. To use the Website, you must be the age of legal majority in your place of residence. By using the Website, you hereby represent that you are at least the age of legal majority in your place of residence. We do not use an application or other mechanism to determine the age of users of the Website. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete information associated with a minor as soon as practicable if we learn that a minor has submitted information to us.

### NOTE FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

California law permits California residents who provide us with personal information to request certain information regarding our disclosure of such information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not, at this time, disclose such information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If we change this policy, we will update this provision and provide instructions on how you may make a request for details. If any other state enacts a similar law as the California law, then this provision will also apply to such state.

### DO-NOT-TRACK DISCLOSURE; THIRD PARTY TRACKING

Certain mechanisms may allow you to send web browser signals, known as “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) signals, indicating your choice to disable tracking on the Website. We do not respond to browser do not track signals at this time. We may not be aware of or able to honor and respond to every such mechanism. More information about “do not track” is available at [www.allaboutdnt.org](http://www.allaboutdnt.org/) concerning such information.

Third parties, other than our vendors (such as our website analytics provider), do not have authorization from us to track which websites you visited prior to and after visiting the Site. That said, we cannot control third party tracking and there may be some third party tracking that occurs without our knowledge or consent.

### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes we make to this Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page. The updated Privacy Policy will take effect as soon as it has been updated or otherwise communicated to you.

## QUESTIONS/CONTACT US

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the way we use your personal information, you can contact us by:

Email: [support@sprint.ly](mailto:support@sprint.ly)

Mail: 970 W Broadway Ste E-152 Jackson WY 83001

This Privacy Policy was last updated in and is effective as of May 25, 2018. This Privacy Policy replaces in its entirety our prior Privacy Policy posted on Sprint.ly dated 11/18/2012.
